The End
Fort side territory reduced by 20%
Damage to the fleet is minimal, sir.
it appears we're under attack doesn't it everyone stand at the ready i must say this is quite
unusual it shouldn't be possible for another realizer to use invisible i'm picking up heat
waste get ready for a second attack all right let's stay focused lose invisible and avoid
also divert all power away from the basic realizers instead let's use everything we've
got to deploy protect territory right yes sir
delightful i didn't expect us to be attacked from the front like this oh i'm cocky of them
their arrogance is getting me hot oh it's making me crazy oh yeah that's what i'm talking about baby
at this rate they'll bring us down
hey jizaki everything okay over there oh wait right let me guess kanazuki is pissing everyone
off well sort of but that's not the problem we're under attack we need you to take over
please help us is that really all you're worried about relax it'll be fine kanazuki knows what he's
doing i'm sure he's got it under control
oh no it's not come on things we just get done and then you have to go and turn off your stupid
chief exes
i swear you've always been a martyr taking everything on yourself refusing to ask for help
reputation i reject that and i throw those words right back in your direction
because you're no different
this isn't how it's supposed to be stop this i know you love each other so why don't you act
like it jito be careful we're not alone
what are they model number dd-007
van der snatch
alan
activate protect territory at one o'clock please range coordinates x 132 y 50 z 39 range 255 246
we've been patiently waiting for the perfect opportunity to catch you alone hello princess
though i have to admit i'm surprised those things i didn't realize they were spirits much less a single
being split in two parts cut the crap and get to it you're with ast aren't you so then you know
all about the defense forces anti-spirit team impressive unfortunately that's incorrect
shito you all right yeah well it appears you're the real deal nicely done
princess why don't you do us all a favor and come with me right now if you oblige me i promise i'll make
it worth your while shut your mouth calm down no matter what she's up to it's a bad idea to point
that at anyone hold on a bit i don't know what it is exactly but something's wrong this woman
i have a bad feeling about her it's like she's an overpowered version of an ast
that's an interesting way to put it bandersnatch squad keep your distance for now
i'm gonna find out how good this little princess really is it's put up or shut up time
bring it on
sir the ship is holding up no damage yet if protect territory is applied to a pinpoint location it's
even more effective who knows with this strategy and a little bit of luck it might survive this
attack after all yes possibly but what about the rest of the ship sir we're completely vulnerable
everywhere else next up specifying range in the same direction five zero six nine that range is far
too narrow hurry up or we're dead and it'll be a painful death but you know that doesn't sound all
bad plus sometimes bad is good oh yeah range five zero six nine that's true deploy
this attack was even stronger than the one before so that's why he made
the range so little relax it'll be fine kanazuki knows what he's doing
come on is that really all you've got princess i was looking forward to this i even equipped pin
dragon point what a disappointment time to end this
tokka i'm coming stop this now i think not first make sure our guest is unconscious and then take her
back to back to the arbiter
damn you let her go what do you bastards think you're doing
tokka stop it
oh no there's nothing i can do this can't be happening not again
no i refuse to feel helpless
oh god
the
oh
we're fine no damage it was blocked again if i wasn't concerned for the ship i'd welcome a few
more attacks it's the truth they really get me hot and make me feel so dirty prepare the magic
power cannon mistletane engage
damn him damn that stupid bastard turn all ashcroft betas channels one through fifty up to maximum
power immediately let's end this full speed ahead shave off the enemy ship's territory
how can this be how are you holding sample fun what are you shido itsuka i thought you were a human
i am a human well more or less i do believe i've changed my mind i'd like for you to come with
me as well resisting us would not be wise it's mistletane the cannon's been evading oh well
i've never been good at attacking i'm better at taking pain i never really thought about giving it
incoming the enemy is heading this way interesting those naughty little boys have come to shave off
our territory directly activate the basic realizers with parallel driving force bring all generated
magic power to the territory roger ar zero zero eight device one through ten initialize drive force
engage oh i almost forgot the most important thing leave one control realizer as is and send the rest to
generate power please copy that but what will control the magic power don't worry i have a plan in mind
just wait and see enemy ship territory output rising ha what kind of fool are you trying to ambush the
orbitale territory coming into contact territory deploy raid condense the entire attack to the point of contact we'll flatten them with one blow
roger that territory deploy range now
our territory output is even with theirs but by contracting the orbitale's range we grow stronger which gives us a clear upper hand
yes i've won victory is mine
bandersnatch squad take him into custody if he resists break his arms
if he still resists break his legs too
what happened we've been hit impact on the starboard side sir
it's impossible how can this be captain severe damage was sustained in the b2 sector the control room is on fire
what the hell the bandersnatch squad has gone completely haywire down here does somebody want to fill me in
wait the control room's under attack no that's not possible
why are you engaged with an airship i don't remember giving that order
come on toka let's go quick after them
what in the hell is going on
no this can't be it's not fair
i'm i am the greatest wizard in all the land
crap
hey guys remember when we like dug all of those traps
i'm pretty sure there's one out there that no one ever got caught in
well who knows maybe we hid it too well
that is so lame
look the enemy ship is retreating
hey hold on a sec
do you see that
what's going on
he just generated a territory
from the geek trifolium realizer
we're attacking the enemy ship like a mine
he may be unconventional and a whole lot on the weird side
but he knows what he's doing
kaguya yuzuru stop it right now
listen to me please don't do this there might be a way for both of you to live
i know
this will get their attention
hey
no luck
damn
come on
just look
over here
kaguya yuzuru
hearing the passion in your voice
i'd be lying to you if i said i wasn't a bit jealous
what should i do
how do i stop them
you summoned sandalfon
you brought forth its power with your desire shito
you see it answered your call and only you have the power to command it now
only me
but how
help me
calm your heart and still your mind
what do you want at this moment
focus on your desire and let everything else go
let your wish come to the forefront of all your senses
nothing else in the world matters right now
just this
picture what you want
yearn for it in the depths of your heart and swing with everything you have
please trust me
do this and the angel will be by your side
such unease turmoil
listen to me stop it
right now
this fighting has to end
you just don't get it do you shito
this doesn't have anything to do with you anymore
agreement
please do not come between us shito
no you're wrong
i get to pick the winner of this duel
that hasn't changed a bit
did you hear what i said
the true yamai will be decided by me
i've made my decision
and i choose
both of you
you can't be serious
what are you stupid
scorn
that answer is entirely absurd
maybe so but that's my answer
you both have your strengths
but neither of you are more deserving than the other
so it's impossible to pick
kaguya
you care about yuzuru more than she cares for herself
and yuzuru
the same is true of how you feel about kaguya
if you won't accept my decision then figure it out yourselves
here are your options
one
yuzuru takes in kaguya and becomes the true yamai
two
kaguya takes in yuzuru and becomes the true yamai
that's easy
three
in exchange for losing all your spirit powers
you both get to live
sorry
but i always prefer to have a third option in situations like these
either or really isn't my style
now it's time for you to choose
what are you saying
doubt
it won't work
yes it will
trust me okay
i promise
look
the only thing i'm asking is that you give me the chance to help you survive
you're just a human
and humans don't have the power to do that
maybe i do
remember i'm the one who split that wind you're so proud of
if i fail
you can kill me for all i care
please
no
well any thoughts speak up
disbelief
for a human being to have that ability seems unlikely
i know right
but the little twerp won't leave us be
he's interrupted our duels twice the annoying brat
concur
i was rapidly nearing the point of defeating you once and for all and letting you survive in my place
not to burst your bubble but that wasn't gonna happen
i was gonna win and let you survive
hey yuzuru
reply
what is it
well
this is all purely hypothetical
but what if shido's actually right
and we can both live
response
i would like it
that would make me happy
jeez
you're unexpectedly romantic
protest
no more so than you are
yeah i suppose you're right i am
question
if we could both survive like he said
what would be the first thing you would do
huh
good question
oh
i think i'd want to try that kinako bread toka told us about
apparently it's pretty delicious
agreement
i would enjoy that as well
what about you yuzuru
answer
i would like to try going to school
that sounds awesome
the boys would be all over you from day one
they wouldn't know what to do with themselves
negative
i believe you are exaggerating
if anything the boys would come after you
do you really think so
correct
of course this is all just hypothetical
yeah
that's true
but hypothetically
we could stroll around town after school right
agreement
i would also like to go to a cafe
sounds good but
we're definitely splitting the check
negative
you are buying
after all
you eat more than i do
come on i don't eat that much food
error
yes you do
yuzuru
reply
what is it
i'm sorry
will you forgive me for lying to you
i
i know i said i did but i don't want to die
i just want to live
with you
i want us to be together a little longer
reply
i concur
i don't want to disappear
i want to be by your side kaguya
yuzuru
kaguya
captain
we can't lower our altitude any more than this
the residents will notice us
do as you're told
i'm not leaving this fight with my tail tucked between my legs like some coward
deploy all bandersnatch left in the ship right away
i'll capture them myself if i have to
i will not leave here empty-handed
this is just getting ridiculous
agreement
i do wish they could take a hint
i've got an idea
wanna play
affirmative
let's put an end to this
drop by el
el cadal
What do you want?
Well, I'm glad to see you're awake.
Yeah, me too.
But wait, what happened?
When that machine attacked us, you intervened.
It knocked you unconscious, but thankfully stopped moving after.
I owe you far more than I can ever repay.
You saved my life.
What about Shido? He's in danger.
Don't push yourself too hard.
He'll be back soon, I have no doubt.
I want to be strong and powerful.
Not for myself, but so I can protect him.
Hey, Shido, we want to thank you for everything.
It means a lot. We won't forget.
Indeed. Sincere thanks.
We will both be in your debt forever.
It's no big deal.
It is. And as a way of properly thanking you,
we'd like to give you a gift.
Petition. Please close your eyes immediately.
Huh? Oh, right.
Whoa! Hey, what the heck do you think you're doing?
Thanking you, silly.
I already told you.
What's wrong? Did you not like it?
Dismay! How indecent!
Wait, just calm down.
I didn't have a choice.
I know it's weird,
but this is what happens when your powers are sealed.
Shido, what was that bright light?
What in the world is going on here?
This is not what it looks like!
We tried to thank Shido,
and then he made our claws disappear.
Depression.
Now I'll never find a suitable husband.
No, you've got it all wrong, I swear!
Shido!
I have confirmation.
There's no mistake.
Tokoyotagami is the spirit princess.
I see.
At the very least,
we confirmed what we needed to know,
which makes this mission a success.
Good work.
Return to base.
Right.
Do I have permission to ask you a question, sir?
Be quick about it.
Do you think it's possible
that there's a human being
who can handle the power of the spirits?
Or would you say that's a ridiculous notion?
それは、それは、果てない旅
キミを救う勇者の物語
あるお籍の国
旅立 tower勇者
桃源 駆け抜け 目指すはお姫玉
真っ暗な洞窟 風吹き荒れる山
孤独 剣をかざして
瞳に映る雪の炎
闇の手を振り払い 君の手を握く
今だって夢だって剣を手に
君のこと見つけるよ闇を裂いて
倒れたって暗くだって負けないから
この手をギュッと捕まえて
消えない雪の炎が
高い照らしている
耳にいる
表 hopeless
ページャーのほか underkumに
大彫りがする
恩が生えれば
よく感じる
vested劣が
もう一気による
さらに逃げて
私は闇の無り
あそらにも
対応力の遅れ
を厚めうか
異動すり
困惑も
祕務を着て
彼らも
sign that is not an option.
I see.
I'm sorry to force such an unpleasant
task on you, but I'm afraid
we have no other choice.
No, I understand, sir. It's like you said.
We have no other choice, and should the worst
come to pass, I'll kill
Shido myself.